UNITE ACWA Jacob Potofsky Memorabilia 6000/042 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE ACWA Jacob Potofsky Memorabilia
1914-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America
Potofsky, Jacob
6000/042 MB
2.11 cubic feet
2.1 linear ft.
Memorabilia.
6082954
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Marcia Clark, September 26, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 12, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Textile industry--New York (State)--New York; Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Clothing trade--New York (State)--New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Hillman, Sidney, 1887-1946; Potofsky, Jacob S.(Jacob Samuel), 1894-1979; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; AFL-CIO --Archives.; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives.; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Pennsylvania Joint Board--Archives; Brandeis University --Archives; Canadian Congress of Labour --Archives; Congress of American-Soviet Friendship -- Archives; Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.) --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives.; New York State Industrial Union Council -- Archives; Oil Workers International Union --Archives; Textile Workers Union of America; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives; United Office and Professional Workers of America --Archives; United Paperworkers of America --Archives; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America; United Steelworkers of America
6082954
- Badges - ACWA, TWUA - 4 badges, 2 name tags -- 1928-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Badges - AFL-CIO, ACTWU -- 6 buttons, badges and name tags -- 1958-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Badges - ILGWU -- 3 badges -- 1956-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Badges - ACWA -- 4 badges -- 1958-1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Badges - ACWA -- 4 badges -- 1946-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Badges - ACWA -- 4 badges -- 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Badges - ACWA -- 4 badges - 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Badges - AFL-CIO -- 7 badges -- 1965-1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Badges - AFL-CIO -- 5 badges -- 1955-1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Badges - ACWA -- 3 badges -- 1939- (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Badges - URCL & PW of A -- 4 badges -- 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Badges and Buttons -- United Public Workers of America -- 3 badges, 3 buttons -- 1953-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Badges - CIO -- 5 badges -- 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Badges - CIO -- 4 badges -- 1946-1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Badges - ACWA -- 4 badges -- 1941-1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Badges - CIO, AFL-CIO -- 6 badges -- 1934-1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Badges - ACWA -- 6 badges -- 1936-1954 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Badges - ACWA -- 6 badges -- 1920-1944 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Badges - ACWA -- 5 badges -- 1930-1956 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Badges - New York State Industrial Union Council -- 3 badges -- 1939-1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Badges - ILGWU, Int'l. Fur Workers Union, National Trade Union Conference for Labor Israel -- 5 badges -- 1934-1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Badges - ACWA, AFL-CIO -- 4 badges, 2 name tags -- 1958-1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Badges - ACWA -- 2 badges -- 1921 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Badges - CIO, ILGWU -- 4 badges -- 1928-1938 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Badges - ACWA, United Paper Workers of America -- 3 badges -- 1924-1944 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Badges, buttons - TWUA, ACWA, UGW of A, CIO -- 6 items -- 1914-1936 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Scope and Contents
  2 photos of badges that were very moldy and not kept
- Badges - CIO -- 6 badges -- 1938-1952 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Badges - New York State Industrial Union Council, Aluminum Workers of America -- 6 badges -- 1942-1956 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Badges - ACWA, ILGWU -- 6 badges -- 1934-1956 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Badges - CIO -- 4 badges -- 1941-1948 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Badges - CIO - 4 badges -- some water damage -- 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Badges - TWUA, ACTWA, United Rubber Workers of America -- 1941-1950 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Jacob Potofsky - Brandeis Univ. Honorary Degree (Box 3)
  - Jacob Potofsky - Brandeis Univ. Honorary Degree (Box 3, Folder 1)